Spalek, John M.; Papers ger106
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Photographs, Undated; 2
  - Hannah Arendt, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Austin Riggs Center, Stockbridge, MA, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Julius Bab, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Leo Baeck, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Rudolf Baer, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Ernst Barlach, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Frederick Bauer, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Max Beckmann, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Richard Beer-Hofmann, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Martin Beradt, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Richard Berczeller, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Alban Berg, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Friedrich Bergammer, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Martha Berges, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Emil Bernhard-Cohn, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Curt (Kurt) Bernhardt, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Hans A. Bethe, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Otto Bettmann, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Bruno Bettelheim, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Black Mountain College; Anni Albers; Heinrich Jalowetz; Edward Lowinsky; Erwin Straus, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Felix Bloch, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Dietrich von Bodenstein, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Erwin Bodky. Also programs, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Niels Bohr, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Joseph Braunstein, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Arnold Brecht, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Bertolt Brecht; Johannes R. Becher, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 35)
  - Hermann Broch, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 36)
  - Max Brod, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 37)
  - Ferdinand Bruckner, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 38)
  - Heinrich Brning, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 39)
  - Ernest Bueding, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 40)
  - Wilhelm Buschke, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 41)
  - Elias Canetti, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 42)
  - Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 43)
  - Richard Nikolaus Graf von Coudenhove-Kalergi, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 44)
  - Richard Courant, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 45)
  - Max Delbrck, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 46)
  - Ren D'Harnoncourt, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 47)
  - William (Wilhelm) Dieterle, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 48)
  - Marlene Dietrich, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 49)
  - Benedikt F. Dolbin, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 50)
  - Rudolf Eckstein, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 51)
  - Alice Ehlers, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 52)
  - Otto Ehrlich, Undated (Box 1 (2-Photographs), Folder 53)
  - Albert Einstein, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Frederick R. Eirich (group photo), Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Egon Eis, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Walter Maurice Elsasser, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Emergency Committee of Atomic Scientists, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Emergency Rescue Committee, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Richard Ettinghausen, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Exile: Book burnings, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Exile: Preussische Akademie der Knste (Prussian Academy of the Arts), Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Enrico Fermi, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Lion Feuchtwanger; Marta Feuchtwanger; Heinrich Mann, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - James Franck, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Bruno Frank; Liesl Frank Lustig; Albert Bassermann, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Leonhard Frank, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Erich Fried, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Otto Frisch, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Kurt von Fritz, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - George Froeschel; Elsa Froeschel; Gina Kaus, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Ren Flp-Miller, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - J. Herbert Furth, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - George Gamow, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Manfred George; Eleanor Roosevelt; Theodor Heuss, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Salom Gluecksohn-Waelsch, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Alexander Gode von Aesch, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Curt Goetz, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Oskar Maria Graf, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Walter Gropius, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - George Grosz; Elisabeth Bergner, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Victor Gruen, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Willy Haas, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Hans Habe, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Frederick Hacker; Max Horkheimer, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Otto Hahn; Ernest Rutherford; Ernest Rutherford, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Otto von Hapsburg (letter text), Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Iwan Heilbut, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 35)
  - Werner Heisenberg, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 36)
  - Gertrude Henle; Werner Henle, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 37)
  - Dietrich von Hildebrand, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 38)
  - Paul Hindemith, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 39)
  - Felix Hirsch; Elisabeth F. Hirsch, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 40)
  - Albert O. Hirschman, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 41)
  - Adolf Hitler, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 42)
  - Fritz Hochwlder, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 43)
  - Franz Hoellering, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 44)
  - Arnold Hllriegel, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 45)
  - Louise Holborn, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 46)
  - Karen Horney; Carl Zuckmayer, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 47)
  - Erich Hula, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 48)
  - Institute for Psychoanalysis (Los Angeles, San Francisco), Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 49)
  - Eric Isenburger, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 50)
  - Heinrich Eduard Jacob, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 51)
  - Felix Jackson (Felix Joachimson), Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 52)
  - Walter Jahrreis, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 53)
  - Horst Waldemar Janson, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 54)
  - Hans Jaray; Oskar Karlweis; John Wengraf, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 55)
  - Leopold Jessner, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 56)
  - Alvin Johnson, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 57)
  - Hans (John) Kafka, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 58)
  - Erich von Kahler, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 59)
  - Georg Kaiser, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 60)
  - Mascha Kaleko, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 61)
  - Joseph Kaskell, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 62)
  - Hans Kaunitz, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 63)
  - Hermann Kesten, Undated (Box 2 (2-Photographs), Folder 64)
  - Otto Kirchheimer, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Otto Klemperer, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Max Knight, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Henry Koerner (TIME magazine covers); Rudolf Bing; George Szell, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Arthur Koestler, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Frederick Kohner, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Walter Kohner, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Leopoldine Konstantin, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Fritz Kortner, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Henry Koster, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Mrs. Julius Kraft, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Stephan Lackner; Thomas Mann, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Peter Martin Lampel, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Helmut Erich Landsberg, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Else Lasker-Schler, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Paul Lazarsfeld, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Emil Lederer, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Lotte Lenya; Kurt Weill, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Peter M. Lindt, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Peter Lorre, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Los Alamos Scientific Laboratories, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Emil Ludwig; Bruno Walter, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Jan Lustig, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Liesl Frank Lustig; Fritzi Massary, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Joachim Maass, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Alma Mahler-Werfel, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Manchester Guardian list of dismissed scholars, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Golo Mann, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Klaus Mann, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Thomas Mann; Erika Mann; Heinrich Mann, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Valeriu Marcu, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Ludwig Marcuse; Sascha Marcuse, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Hermann Mark, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - George Marton, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Gertie Marx, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 35)
  - Josef Marx, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 36)
  - Fritzi Massary, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 37)
  - Ernst Moritz Manasse, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 38)
  - Maria Goeppert Mayer, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 39)
  - Lisa Meitner, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 40)
  - Karl Menninger; Menninger Clinic, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 41)
  - Karl Meyer, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 42)
  - Otto Meyerhof, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 43)
  - Ludwig Mies van der Rohe, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 44)
  - Franz Molnar (Ferenc Neumann), Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 45)
  - Oskar Morgenstern, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 46)
  - Soma Morgenstern, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 47)
  - Hans Morgenthau, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 48)
  - Norbert Muhlen; Theodor Heuss; Melvin Laskey, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 49)
  - Robert Musil, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 50)
  - David Nachmansohn, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 51)
  - Hans Namuth, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 52)
  - Helmuth Nathan, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 53)
  - Hans Natonek, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 54)
  - Hans Neisser, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 55)
  - Fritz Neugass; Hans Arp, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 56)
  - New School for Social Research (group photo: Julie Meyer; Horace Kallen; Frieda Wunderlich; Felix Kaufmann; Erich Hula; Alvin Johnson; Clara Mayer; Hans Staudinger; Arnold Brecht; Kurt Riezler; Bryn Hovde; Albert Salomon; Leo Strauss; Solomon Asch; Hans Neisser; Mary Henle; Abba Lerner; Adolph Lowe; Carl Mayer; Eduard Heimann; Willy Brandt), Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 57)
  - New School Theatre Workshop, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 58)
  - John Robert Oppenheimer, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 59)
  - Alfred Oppler, Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 60)
  - Henry Pachter (Heinz Pchter), Undated (Box 3 (2-Photographs), Folder 61)
  - Elizabeth Paetel, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Karl Otto Paetel (early photos), Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Karl Otto Paetel (later photos), Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Karl Otto Paetel, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Karl Otto Paetel -- Associates; Joseph Buttinger; Joseph Drexel; Ernst Niekisch; Max Wehling, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Hertha Pauli, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Wolfgang Pauli, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Yella Pessl, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Physics Conference, Rome, 1931 (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - Jacob Picard, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Erwin Piscator, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Alfred Polgar, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Otto Preminger, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Karl Pribram, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Hans Rademacher, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Franz Rapp, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Reichstag burning, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Theodor Reik, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Max Reinhardt, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Walter Reisch, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Erich Maria Remarque; Paulette Goddard; Sam Salz, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Kurt Rietzler, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - George Rohrlich, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Joseph Roth, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Ludwig Roth, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Miklos Rozsa, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Udo Rukser, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Nelly Sachs, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Hans Sahl, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Die Sammlung, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Bertha Scharrer; Ernst Scharrer, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - David Scherf, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Alfred Schick, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Eric Schiff, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Joseph Schildkraut, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 35)
  - Magdalena Schoch, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 36)
  - Arnold Schoenberg, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 37)
  - Franz Schoenberner, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 38)
  - Rudolf Schnheimer, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 39)
  - Richard Schuler, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 40)
  - Schultz-Wittenborn, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 41)
  - Heinz Schultz, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 42)
  - Kurt von Schuschnigg, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 43)
  - Alfred Schutz, Undated (Box 4 (2-Photographs), Folder 44)
  - Anna Seghers. Published photo only, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Rudolf Serkin; Erich Leinsdorf; Erich Leinsdorf, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Curt Siodmak, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - William (Wilhelm) Sollmann, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Wilhelm Speyer, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 5)
  - Mme. Greta Stauber. Program, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 6)
  - Fred Stein; also list of Fred Stein portraits, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 7)
  - Hans Steinitz, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 8)
  - Fritz Strassmann, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 9)
  - August Strindberg, Production of Dream Play, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 10)
  - Leo Szilard, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 11)
  - Walter Taussig, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 12)
  - Olga Taussky-Todd, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 13)
  - Edward Teller, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 14)
  - Albert Theile, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 15)
  - Paul Tillich; Bishop Otto Dibelius; Walter Reuther, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 16)
  - Hans Tischler, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 17)
  - Ernst Toch; William Steinberg, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 18)
  - Friedrich Torberg, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 19)
  - Arturo Toscanini; Bruno Walter; Stefan Zweig, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 20)
  - Trapp Family Choir. Program, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 21)
  - Fritz von Unruh, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 22)
  - Johannes Urzidil, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 23)
  - Osso Vaneyss (Otto Eis), Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 24)
  - Berthold Viertel; Albert Einstein, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 25)
  - Abraham Wald, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 26)
  - Joseph Wechsberg, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 27)
  - Frank Wedekind, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 28)
  - Helene Weigel, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 29)
  - Karl Weigl; Vally Weigl, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 30)
  - Egon Weiss, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 31)
  - Victor Weisskopf, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 32)
  - Gisela Werbezirk, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 33)
  - Franz Werfel, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 34)
  - Alfred Werner, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 35)
  - Eric Werner, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 36)
  - Walter Wicclair, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 37)
  - Eugene Wigner; Rudolf Ladenburg, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 38)
  - Billy Wilder, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 39)
  - Werner Wille, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 40)
  - George Winter, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 41)
  - Alfred Wolfenstein, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 42)
  - Kurt Wolff; Gunter Grass, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 43)
  - Victoria Wolff, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 44)
  - Karl Wolfskehl, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 45)
  - Julius Wyler, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 46)
  - Eric Zeisl, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 47)
  - Guido Zernatto, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 48)
  - Carl Zuckmayer, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 49)
  - Stefan Zweig; Friederike Zweig, Scholem Asch, Undated (Box 5 (2-Photographs), Folder 50)
  - Oskar Maria Graf; Bertolt Brecht, Undated (Box 6 (2-Photographs), Folder 1)
  - Oskar Maria Graf; Jacob Blauner, Undated (Box 6 (2-Photographs), Folder 2)
  - Lotte Jacobi, Undated (Box 6 (2-Photographs), Folder 3)
  - Walter Maria Kotschnig, Undated (Box 6 (2-Photographs), Folder 4)
  - Yella Pessl, Undated (Box 6 (2-Photographs), Folder 5)